here are the stories were covering this
hanc narrationem hic tegebant
week in the category 5 TV newsrooms a
V in hebdomadam genus a TV Newsrooms
San Francisco startup is 3d printing
San Francisco startup est 3D printing
entire houses in just one day a new
uno die tota domus novae
method of storing data in DNA stores 215
stores modum repono notitia in DNA CCXV
petabytes of data in a single gram of
petabytes data est in unum de gram
DNA robots with real muscles and skin it
Robots cum ipsa pelle ea nervi et carnes DNA
could become a thing sooner than we
quam citius potuit aliquid nobis facti sunt
imagined and the nintendo switch is
et Nintendo est switch excogitari
having big problems with its little
qui cum parva quaestiones
screen these stories are coming right up
talia sunt usque protegant
don't go anywhere Jeff Weston Yellin
non usquam Jeff Weston Yellin
you're building a brand new beautiful
Pulchra es novam in aedificationem
website what are you alright you're
Bene vos audio quis tu es website
terrible actor what this we're acting
Terribilis est actor huius erant 'quod agens
comes into play I don't know where
iungitur nescio quo
Arctic you're supposed to act okay I'm
Spanis vestri 'supponitur agere Im' okay
building a really cool website are you
building a vere frigus es website
building a really cool website you need
building a vere frigus Pagina quam indigere
hosting one of the things about a
hosting est unum de
hosting account if you don't want to
si autem non vis ad rationem hosting
have limitations put on your website
et posuit limitations in vestri website
it's true how much hard drive space you
ferreus coegi locus suus 'verum, quanto te,
have how many email accounts how many
Quot quot autem email rationum
domains can point to it well we've got
Potest etiam ea quae ad domains Comperto
an amazing deal for you for a very
multum enim mirabile est quia per ipsum
limited time cat five dot TV / dreamhost
tunc cattus quinque dat limitata TV / dreamhost
for just five dollars and a bit of
et quinque pupa et justum aliquantulus of
change per month you are going to get
ut per mutationem mensis tu properas
unlimited web site hosting unlimited
web hosting site infinitus infinitus
email accounts on that hosting service
hosting servitium email rationum eo
you are also going to receive a free
libera etiam acceptura es
domain name the route put your own com
iter suum com domain nomen tuum
site to put that amazing website be even
et quod mirabile est, quod website locum ad induendum
working on on there if you run if you
quod si tu curris noctu in
want to build a wordpress site fine sign
volo wordpress site est bene facere signum
up cat5 TV / dreamhost don't forget
CAT5 in TV / dreamhost ne obliviscaris
about papers on it just don't do it but
sed hoc non est iustus non est de papers
hey it's a great deal folk best deal
heu suus 'optimus paciscor plurimum vulgares
you're going to find five dollars and
vos erant 'iens ut quinque pupa et
change per month go to cap five dot TV /
per mutationem mense ad quinque cap dat TV /
dreamhost I'm sassage' Madison here the
dreamhost sassage Im 'qui hic Madison
top stories for the week of march eight
Top VIII Martiis hebdomadarius
2017 a san francisco-based 3d printing
San Francisco-printing fundatur in MMXVII 3D
startup Ava score has come up with an
cum autem venerit score startup ava
exceedingly affordable solution for
valde parabilis solutio
building new houses they can 3d print
3d tecta novantem possunt print
concrete walls for a small house in
et muri in re parva domus
under 24 hours what I know Tom cars one
in XXIV horas scire quid cars Tom unum
day a fifth Corps recently used its
quintus dies, a Corps nuper usus eius
massive 3d printer to lay down concrete
3D typographus ingens ponere certum
walls on a test home in a site in Russia
muri super domum in test situ in Russia
where it has a business partner printing
ubi non est negotium socium printing
out a cozy but livable 400 square foot
livable, sed ex CD quadratum pedem CONMODUS
house the machine which looks more like
domus, quae spectat similior machina
a small crane than a conventional 3d
parva 3D machina sua quam conventional
printer spits out layer upon layer of
procer in accumsan accumsan respuat
concrete mixture a concrete mixture is
mixtisque Concretum uero concretum est mixtisque
that the company says can last for 175
Dicit enim societas durare potest CLXXV
years after printing out the walls the
postquam e muris excudendi
printer is removed and a group of
est enim coetus atque remota a printer
contractors install insulation windows
Nulla itaque redemptoribus install Fenestra
appliances and a roof it's not entirely
illud omnino tecta appliances
clear whether the whole house was
patet num in tota domo eius
finished and furnished in 24 hours or
XXIV horas praebita et conplevit
whether or not the walls were just
moenibus essent necne
printed in that time the company says
typis in illo tempore cum turba dixit
that it can build and furnish these
Haec saltem ut adiuuarent
small houses for cost of about ten
Nam pretium decem domunculas
thousand dollars and according to the
iuxta centena
company's blog on the project the
project comitatu scriptor blog est super
windows and doors or by far the most
et fenestrae clausae longe
expensive components these houses could
quibus poterat amet lacinia
be used to how quickly rehoused those
quomodo his utendum cito rehoused
affected by natural disasters the
est affectus naturalis clades
company said they might also be of use
Dixerunt etiam prodesse cum
in its own home town where an influx of
unde influxus in sua civitate
technology workers in recent years has
operarios in technology habet annis
created housing shortage cry was in
shortage clamor in habitationi creata est
Kurdish crisis one city I'm excited
Lingua Kurdica discrimen inter me urbe concitatae
about this oh my gosh this is cool so I
utinam frigidus ut haec mea est gosh
asked me get back to Jamaica for a
interrogavit me ut revertar in Iamaica est
second so alright month ok so in Jamaica
ita licet secunda mensis ok ut Jamaica
Jamaicans they don't go into debt to
Non debebat intrare Jamaicans
build their houses so they save up money
Dederunt autem pecunias servare domos suas
and they buy a cinder block right then
et emere ius deinde spodium obstructionum
they say about more money in with my a
dic mihi per circuitum non amplius pecunia et in
cinder block and then block at a time
spodium scandalum et impedit tempore
I'm talkative time and they build their
EGO sum aedificium suum constituant, et tunc garrula,
houses one room at a time out of cinder
qui locus ex eo tempore cinerem domos
block nice houses have just had a lot of
domos pulchras scandalum iam multum
years put in sure right but if this is
annis certo in jure, si hoc verum est,
only ten thousand dollars furnished
decies centena instructus
right so now oftentimes these houses
nunc iure reclament domibus istis
don't have windows like they have
Non habent sicut fenestras
Windows spaces but not actual windows
Fenestra, non autem ipsa spatia fenestras
because they do take more money and time
eo tempore ceperint amplius
yeah but that is incredible for
yeah qui autem res incredibilis credita est
countries like that right absolutely but
quia jus non absolute similis terris
with windows and doors being said to be
et per fenestras portae quae locutus est
the most expensive component but it
sed pars carissimum
still is done within a ten thousand
fit tamen intra decem
all our budget yeah and and hopefully
yeah, et omne budget nostris in votis
yeah and that's the cool thing too is
yeah, et frigus res est ut is quoque
that I'm one of those people who follows
Im 'unus illorum populus, qui sequitur me
the tiny house movement yes and it's
ad minima domus motus et sic suus '
just like somebody like all right square
sicut omnia quadrata alium
feet is perfect yeah so it's like as a
memini sicut perfectior est et pedes
young adult like being 22 years old I
ut esse iuvenes adult XXII annorum sum
can't really mortgage your house yeah
non potest vere in tributa regis yeah domum tuam
renting is another option but hey yeah
optio sed est alius conductione heus yeah
get your own plot of land and there we
Emitque partem agri, et ut tua ibi
go I mean great and it takes like 15
ut non sit magnus et quasi XV capit
minutes to clean 400 square feet exactly
CD quadratum pedes ad minutis prorsus emundare
we get a lot of cement dust yes you can
Vos can etiam adepto multum caementa pulvis sumus
be a tech tech not was it technology
Non enim erit tech technology tech
minimalist right where you own a lot of
minimalist iure quo multum habent
things but it's all only on your
rebus omnibus, sed suus 'non in vestri
computer and yes put solar panels on the
Etiam posuit a solaris tabulata PC
roof that's not a turbine and you're off
Quod ut 'non nimium off et tectum Turbine
the grid can see some really cool uses
in malesuada euismod potest videre aliquid realiter frigus usus,
for that even ya think about that as a
quod etiam cogitare de illa ut ya
cottager or something like that too yeah
aut sicut aliquid, quod etiam cotmannus yeah
and again even said like for housing
et iterum dixerunt quidem quia, sicut habitationi
crisis and like a disasters and stuff
et est discrimen sicut et supellectilem clades
too that's huge or even the homeless
vel etiam ut 'ingens profugo
population right so lots of places where
population locis ubi ex jure et lots
there's just a settlement of homeless
Ibi suus 'iustus a res of profugo
people it wouldn't take a lot of money
noluit gentem opibus
to actually fund ring up and have a set
ut ipsa anulum fiscus et a paro
of 20 of those houses and have them just
XX De his modo illis domos
a free stop in place right maybe have
libera subsisto in loco ius habent maybe
them patrol some foundation nice to be
nisi aliquo fundamento in illis Boii
created or adopt this as something that
aut sicut aliquid, quod hoc capere creata est
they do because if it can be done this
si id fieri faciant
cheaply and and i would expect there's
et illic parvo et plerumque
less parts to move i think about this
minus mihi de hac parte movere
reminds me a little bit of modular homes
admonuit me paululum domos modulares
the modular homes they have to be
modulari oportet domos
transported they're built in a factory
Lorem officinas traducti exstructas
and they're brought there and there's a
et intulit illuc, et erant illic 'a
lot of there's a lot of carbon footprint
illic 'multus of multus of carbo carbonis vestigium,
there's a lot of in comparison well this
illic 'multus of bene est in hac collatio
is this is concrete being poured at the
sequitur subiectum, in quo est infudit
site by a 3d printer thank you i love i
situs a printer 3D te amo ego gratias ago tibi,
love the thought even in in the state's
si quidem in publico amet
there's a tornado alley or whatever yeah
Gaudete quidquid ibi angiportum turbo
right concrete is a pretty solid note
ius certum est pulchellus solidum nota
exactly concrete's not go away okay sure
prorsus re bene certus suus 'non auferetur
yeah other than what I live in one I
yeah praeter ea quae ego habito in unum
think it'd look like this gonna be a
Curabitur sit amet putes viderem
great news week door number winding
curva dedere portae octo numero magna nuntium
honey okay what do you got for us next
mel bene nobis quid tibi got postero
ten years ago if you wanted to back up
decem annos ut si vos volo tergum sursum
some of your old photos you might have
Quidam veterum imaginibus non haberet
stored them on a big clunky external
reponuntur in externis magna clunky
hard drive that wait a couple of pounds
ferreus coegi bilibris sperant
and with a pain to lug around it's true
et cum dolore ad TRAHO circa verum est
I might I might have done that you might
Ut essem vobis possem
have done it mm-hmm can you
Hmm feci mm potes
now you may back at all back up all the
ut omnes retro cunctos iam
data from your entire life on just a few
tota vita data paucis
grams of DNA embedded in the code of
P. DNA embedded in a codice
life researchers have now encoded a 1895
Inquisitores vitae nunc est encoded MDCCCXCV
French film a computer virus and a
Gallica amet a computer et virum
fifty-dollar amazon gift card this is
centum pupa est Amazon Card
not the first time scientists have
Non primum scientists have
turned to the double helix for storage
convertit in duplici repono pro Helix
but it has always been difficult to
non autem semper fuit difficile est
encode more than a few hundred
quam pauci centum encode
characters of data without turning it
absque notitia de characteribus et convertendi
into an undecipherable mess in their new
et in cibum in novum undecipherable
paper own on friday in science a yaniv
on Friday, in charta habent scientiam et yaniv
out of Ehrlich Jenna Ehrlich and Dina
Jenna Ehrlich Ehrlich de Dina,
valinsky from the New York genome Center
valinsky de Bacteria in New York Center
in Columbia University respectively
in Columbia University respectively
detail a major improvement their new
novam emendationem in detail a major
method that DNA fountain is able to
fons, qui possit modum DNA
store a total of over two megabytes of
condite in summa duos ex megalocteti
data in 72,000 DNA strands and easily
indicia facile 72,000 DNA canalibus
retrieve it the method allows them to
recuperare et concedit ad modum eos
pack 215 petabytes of data on a single
stipant in una notitia de CCXV petabytes
gram of DNA oh yeah the DNA foundation
DNA in DNA fundamenta gram O yeah
technique is remarkable in its
ars mirum in
resistance to errors and ability to
errores et facultatem ad resistendum
maximize storage capacity of DNA before
DNA in conspectu maximize facultatem repono
we're all walking around with bits of
et omnia circum erant 'ambulans in bits
DNA on our key rings instead of flash
DNA pro nobis clavis annulos mico
drives however sequencing will have to
erit autem scire sequencing drives
become significantly cheaper but that
sed quod facti sunt significantly cheaper
might happen sooner than we realize this
quo celerius fieret detegemus
year Illumina announced plans to bring
Illumina anno consilia nuntiatum to bring
the cost of sequencing an entire human
quanti integrum humanum sequence
genome sequencing down to one hundred
centum et pestis Sequencing
dollars sequencing a few megabytes of
sequence in aliquot centena megalocteti
data would cost a small fraction of that
Data parum constaret fractio
wow I have a quick question though DNA
EGO have a velox wow quaestionem, etsi DNA
yeah so it's enough to give how would
ita satis dare vellet Yeah
you I don't I don't get it well I was
Ego autem non tam me et non habetis:
trying to I'm strongly not to laugh
Im 'non valde rideat me temptatis
laughs way through because right now
Nunc quia per risum
we're caring like USB drives and stuff
sicut nos curam USB agitet et supellectilem
yeah it has of course that's on my good
yeah hoc est utique quod meum est bonum,
actual physical it's a computer right
ipsa suus 'a computer ius corporis
when we're shifting the DNA i was
Cum erant 'Remotio ego eram in DNA
thinking like you i have to like bring a
ut adducam ad te cogitans
hamster my pocket is everywhere I go and
criceta sinum meum, et vade, et sit ubique
me could you just doorstep no man how it
mihi potuit quomodo homo absque te tantum pasci
works is that they're probably like
ut verisimile est, quod operatus es
encoding on like the actual bits of DNA
sicut et in ipsa encoding bits DNA
because like as you know
quia tu scis quia amo
with a computer with a bit it's rather
cum a computer cum suus 'aliquantulus magis
on and off like the banner binary right
et quasi signum binarii bene
so they're probably doing a similar
ita ipsi erant 'forsit faciens similis est
approach with DNA just on like that
DNA similis iustum frequentemus
small and zeros but it's so somehow yeah
atque adeo parva est, sed nescio quo pacto zeros yeah
yeah because like I would want to read
yeah, quia sicut ego volo legere
that paper for like more in-depth
Sicut charta altius
information to see how they are doing
certiores faciant quam
that because make any sense to me like
quoniam sensu, quia nihil facere, sicut mihi
it makes sense for me for like that yeah
yeah, quae facit sensum, quasi per me
great question do that to be fair
Magna quaestio est se facere aequum
scientists are just figuring this out
ex his scientists sunt iustum remanens,
okay so it's okay if it's not quite
si minus bene factum bene est
clear the science behind it too right
ut patet in scientia et ius post tergum
people like ours I feel like we're
ut sentio amo sumus populum nostrum
discovering some things about our own
invenire aliquid de nostra
DNA really sure as far as illnesses go
DNA realiter certus ut iret usque ad exitus incerti
and everything we're just like examining
et omne sumus sicut scrutandis
our own DNA and that's hmmm taken us
capta est nobis, filius Vaivodae nostra DNA et quod suus '
some time and now we're going to be
et nunc aliquamdiu erant 'iens futurus
storing data on to DNA I guess it's not
EGO coniecto ut suus 'non DNA notitia repono
our DNA that on no I don't think so I
Non puto ego quod nostrae DNA
mean this isn't Minority Report all
Minoritas expromere non significare
right you'd have to have it would have
jus habere velis haberet
to be that DNA becomes the data right
data dextra decet esse DNA
yeah because that's that's interesting
quia quod suus 'interesting ut yeah
because it's just thought of a science
suus 'iustus autem putaverunt quia de scientia
science fiction concept because they
quia scientia ficta conceptu
said that they were able to encode an
ut dictum est poterant encode
Amazon before kaisa no but like if they
Non ante sed si Amazon kaisa
can encode an amazon gift card on this
Amazon donum card potest esse in hac encode
does that mean like can you inject
non est qui similis sit tibi potest injiciunt
yourself with like money or something
vel pecunia es
then the / ceiling DNA as well won't it
tunc / laquearia RNA etiam Nolo eam
be impossible to steal data then because
impossibile est igitur quod data esset furantur
you'd have to be I would be any match to
vellem autem esse ut est par esse
the person room railings could it be
persona locus blasphemiae suspiciones potest fieri,
something like that my DNA is the only
quid DNA similis mei, quod solus
DNA that unlocks on that Dinah yeah your
DNA quod ille uias tuas in illo ob stuprum yeah
DNA becomes the decryption key right wow
DNA decryption key quod fit iure wow
we just we just one up to the scientist
Sicut enim in uno sciens non
nicely done faster job guys like it yeah
hic autem fit bene memini Job guys sicut
darn everybody call it a nite nite a
nite et certa omnibus dici darn
chalice let it down yeah okay Oxford
calix bene memini demittere Oxon
University researchers said last week
Ultima septimana dicitur Universitas Inquisitores
that robots dressed in human flesh would
quod robots carne indutus esset in homine
benefit people who need tissue
qui prodesse opus TEXTUS
transplants and not benefit anybody's
transplantatio nec prodesse aliorum scriptor
nightmares scientists are already
quae iam sequuntur somnia scientists
growing muscles bones and many organs in
crescente lacertis tot et ossa eorum in
the lab but these tissues are generally
Hi fere tela Lab
small and simple that's why two
et id quod simplex parva duorum
scientists from Oxford University or
from Oxford University et scientists
proposing that we use humanoid robots to
humanoid robots ferentibus utar, ut
grow engineered tissues instead
crescere fibras pro machinatum,
at present human cells are grown in
nunc crevit in humana cellulis
stationary environments but their report
sed famam eorum stabilem ferendum
suggests that moving humanoids could
insinuat quod movere poterat humanoids
help them develop in a far healthier way
auxilium develop eas in via multo salubrius
in theory I agree researchers Pierre
Inquisitores Petrus in doctrina assentior
Alex MLV and Andrew Carr proposed in the
MLV Andrew and Alex propositus in Carr
latest issue of science robotics that
robotics exitus tardus autem scientiam
robots could wear tissue grafts before
antequam uti possit eget inserit robots
transplantation today sheets of cells
translationi hodie laminas cellularum
are grown in segment tape but the
crevit autem sunt in segmentis dorsalibus tape
scientists say that these fail to mimic
scientists dicunt imitatricem esse volt illa deficient
the real mechanical environment for
realis environment pro mechanica
cells the resulting tissues aren't
inde etiam textus cellulis sunt
accustomed to moving and stretching and
et tendens moveri solent
straining which can introduce problems
retorquent, quae inducere possunt difficultates
when used by patients the scientists say
usus enim cum aegris a scientists dicunt,
it's not only technically possible to do
suus 'non solum technica ratione fieri possit facere
but also scientifically pertinent that
sed scientifice instituendos pertinet illud
this be pursued yes-ish yes fish I like
Et sic sequeretur istud icis sicut pisces
are you scared because this is the robot
quod in robot est qui terrebis
this is like I love robots that I want
hoc est quod amo me amare volo robots
robots to look like robots I'm scared of
robots tamquam de robots timeo
robots looking like people but what does
respiciens autem quod non sicut populus robots
not just be robots like doing jumping
erunt quasi non facit saltum robots
jacks in a lab somewhere and wearing
Lab jacks in quodam loco quis, et amictus
moving like this gel they're sharing
Herpesvirus hominis movere sic illi erant 'sharing
like skin suits I feel like like we're
sicut pellis sumus sicut placet eis causis,
narrowing yeah but growing flesh on
yeah et luto obstruunt crescente in carne
themselves in order so that you know
nosse se tam
jaminator if they need to grow like arm
si postulo ut crescere brachium jaminator
muscles well they can they can just do
musculos possunt bene facere possunt iusta
this over and over all day long like
Haec atque huiusmodi quotidie
being an idea where they test the seats
quo probare sunt entis ideam sedes
did you see that no I didn't oh yeah
vide ne tu te utinam non yeah
there's right and then I don't sit
et iustum est quia non sedens
through commercials no it's nice yeah
suus 'nice quod non est per commercials yeah
ECMO and I you know I haven't been to
Et non fuit in vobis scio enim ego ECMO
ikea ever ever what wow it's like on the
ikea semper semper id quod est simile de wow
other side of the earth you create a
hinc terrae creabis
cheerful haven't if I really like you 35
hilaris autem si vere non similis vobis XXXV
to try order all of my furniture from
de ordine experiri meam supellectilem
amazon use our affiliate links please do
uti affiliate links Amazon nostra placet fac
at ikea they have robots that test the
ut in ipsis experiretur ikea habent robots
furniture on going so today it's like a
sicut hodie, sic suus 'iens die supellectilem
chair from ikea and then they have like
de sella ikea sunt sicut et illi
a little robot bum that sits in it gets
modicum ibi fuerit sedenti bum robot
back up and sits in it and gets back up
ascendit et sedet ad recipiat
forever and ever second shell dressed
et usque in aeternum semper indutus secundum testa
test right so this is what it would do
test facere quod justum est
for the skin right yeah I guess so but
EGO coniecto yeah, sed ut ad recte pellis
it was super creepy it would be creepy
Super foret quod creepy creepy
to look
spectare
up but really good idea for all medical
sed usque idea realiter bonum ad omnes medicinae
team medically and scientifically sounds
medically sonos quadrigis, et scientiam,
like a very viable proposition super
Super ipsum quasi viable propositionis
creepy at all cool sales figures suggest
creepy frigus omnino venditionesque figuras suadeant
nintendo's new hybrid handheld console
Nintendo scriptor Novum handheld console hybrid
which went on sale on Friday had become
Veneris die cum sale, quae erat facti sunt
the fastest selling game console in the
quam celerrime in venditionis venatus console
japanese company's history with many
Iaponica historiam per multos comitatu scriptor
stores selling out on the first day of
reponit super die venditionis
sales and entrepreneur poachers scooping
Sales et malefactores hauriatur parum entrepreneur
them up and selling them for twice the
et vendebant ea dupplici
price the switch can be played both on
switch ad pretium potest tam in played
televisions and as a standalone device
televisions et sicut standalone fabrica
but there's a problem thousands of
sed illic 'a forsit milia
owners of nintendo's new console switch
owners of Nintendo scriptor novum console switch
have complained about dead or stuck
quodque mortui non adhæsit
pixels creating distracting and annoying
elementa creandis carentibus perturbationum
dark squares on their screen that would
utinam ut quadrata nigra umbraculinomina
be horrible Nintendo said that such
Nintendo dixit quod talis horror
pixels were normal and should not be
elementa non sunt normalis
considered a defect in other words it's
suus 'considerari aliquo defectu causatur in aliis verbis
your problem not theirs but one analyst
vestri forsit non illorum, sed unum Analystae
said in response to the online photos
dictum est in responsione ad online photos
that it was unbelievable Nintendo had
quod erat incredibile Nintendo
let them leave the factory on a reddit
Reddit autem relinquant officinas
discussion thread one user said that he
disputationem filum unum, ut dicit usor
had returned his to the store and since
quia thesaurum suum redisset
it was making news the store let him
nuntium dictum faciendi copia est anathema
open boxes for a replacement three more
magis aperta pixides ad oblatas tortor tres
devices had dead pixels before he
consiliis habebat quam elementa mortuis
finally found one that looked ok that is
et vidi unum inveni tandem, quod est ok
a razy so I mean I realized were
Intellexi autem razy ut sit erant
Wednesday and they were released on
Et Mercurii die dimissi
friday so they obviously wanted to
Friday tam manifesto ad voluerunt
really hit their deadline right they
vere ledo ius in suis fatalibus
obviously want a timeout well we've seen
Desidero enim vidi tam manifesto timeout
that pixels before online computer
prius enim elementa computatrum online
screens and stuff but a computer screen
sed a computer screen et supellectilem screens
being this big yeah it's one dead pixel
qui mortuus est magnitudine memini pixel
I hate that there's a dead pixel but at
Sed quod odi illic 'a mortuis pixel procul
least it's you know it's this big and
et hoc est magnum illud quidem nosti
it's one pixel among them right but yeah
Ave verum inter pixel suus dexteram
when you've got a little tiny thing in
quando te possedi paulo minima rem
your hand and there's one dead pixel and
manum tuam, et illic 'pixel et mortuus est
it's only this big it's going to be like
quod suus 'iens futurus tantum magnitudine
a well that's all it takes all is it a
et quoque quod sit omne id et totum capit
problem with the actual screen itself
Difficultas in screen ipsa ipsum
yeah yeah it's the technology behind it
yeah yeah suus 'technology post eam
there's you know millions of little
illic 'parum scitis de millions
lights if one of those lights doesn't
lumina luminibus unus eorum non
work then they're just okay with a lot
tum ipsi bene operari per iustus multum
of potential so the point that I'm
itaque potential quod a puncto ad me
making so they were the push for
ita ut erant dis
timeline to get this out right much the
ut de hoc tanto fas timeline
same as wrote lately with sauce
Scripsi nuper idem condimentum
right yes there's a push to get the
sic enim fas est ut a dis
product out maybe instead of making an
productum e loco faciendi quod maybe
unrealistic timeline actually say to the
quas gignit earum ad aiunt timeline
public listen we're just having some
sicut habens aliquam publicam audi nos
issues right now with the screen and we
nunc in screen et in exitibus
want it to be perfect for you so instead
volo esse perfectum, ut pro te
of March third we're going to release
tertio Martii erant 'iens ut dimittere
this let's let's just say we're going to
Hoc lets 'dicere, sicut et nos erant' iens ut lets '
release it maybe in another month or two
vel duos mensem aliam maybe dimittere eam
just so that you get a maybe eight
ita quod maybe adepto a octo
product and this seems like a good time
videtur quod tempus tellus
to bring up Star Trek discovery why
Quare inventionem Ave educare
pourquoi because they said if it's not
quod si non dixerunt pourquoi
ready yet we know we said may but now
sed dixerunt parati sumus ut nunc scimus
they're saying it's going to be sometime
ipsi erant 'iens ut exsisto suus aliquando dicens
later in 2017 see is that that is my
deinde ut ea in MMXVII sedes mea,
point I can't sleep yeah that but it
Non possum hoc loco somnum sane memini sed etiam
still hurts but wouldn't you rather the
sed potius dolet quod tamen non esset,
perfect product all right definitely
omne jus plane perfecta productum
right I think Star Trek needs to do it
necesse est quod facere jus non cogitant Star Trek
right as does Nintendo and then I know
Nintendo facit ut rectum et nosse me
she'd Samsung need to write samsung said
Curabitur dictum Samsung LG non opus est scribere,
send us your phone back we'll give you
si miseris ad phone dabo
this this or this and it was reasonable
hoc est rationabile, sive hoc esset
and yeah we made a mistake we're gonna
yeah, et nos sumus in errorem amet
we're going to make it make good on that
erant 'iens ut bona illa faciunt eam
mmm Nintendo saying too bad so sad you
ita quoque dicentis Nintendo mmm malo contristari vos,
got dead pixels hmm well I'll retract
Et surrexit mortuus pixels hmm bene se latam retractare
that I bet you I thank you that you will
bet ego gratias ago tibi quia non erit tibi hoc
retract that or they will crash and burn
qui se latam retractare vel mos fragosus et incendent igni
it happens with every game cries that's
omne quod contingit ipsum clamat
that's the issues that we've seen it
quia est proventus ut eam vidi;
throughout the console generations
consolari per generationes
especially for example one more famous
praesertim exemplo clariora
defects was the xbox 360 the red ring of
xbox CCCLX est rufus erat et anulus aliquos defectus
death is right right um and that's
et quod rectum est mors um
that's the thing is that it's a new
ut 'aliquid quod suus' a novo
console it's in its first weeks of jail
prima console est in suo plenitudinem annuae vincula
early stripe we are going to early
mane clavum addidi, ad nos ire diluculo
adopters right we've got so that's why I
Comperto ergo quod dico recti adopters ut '
never pre-ordered it anymore but I'm not
numquam pre-iussit valet ultra, nisi ut non sum
surprised see these defects like there's
Miraris haec vitia sicut ibi
even been talk about issues with the two
Disputatio circa quaestiones et fuit cum duobus
controllers having connection issues oh
magistrae habent connexionem O exitibus
no then trying to like update through
Non ergo ut update ut per trying
software but that's the thing if it's a
sed ut 'res si suus' a software
hardware shoe you can't fix that um so I
fix um, ut sic non possis hardware calceus
think I was not really surprised to hear
Puto eram, mirum non est vere audire
about this unfortunately but then again
tum quod valde dolendum, sed de hoc iterum
I haven't been around at endo for a few
Et circumspiciens endo non pauci
years I think it'll get good and then no
puto youll 'adepto nihil boni et annos
maybe offer like trade in your old one
veteris quis similis tui trade offerre maybe
with dead
et mortuus est
tools for something else maybe
per instrumenta aliquid aliud maybe
traditionally I don't know that they
traditionally nescio quod
will get but we'll see time will tell
sed erit tibi videatur tempus narrabo
listen to a Nintendo this is the way I
audite Nintendo est via mea
think Nintendo should especially if this
si maxime hoc videtur Nintendo
is one of if this is possibly their
si hoc est fortasse
biggest seller of all time and it's only
maximus omnium tempus et suus 'tantum venditor
a couple thousand folks that are
quae fit duobus milibus
reporting this issue but it does sound
hac re sonat sed
like that's bad PR right oh yeah weirdo
ut recta PR o Malae yeah weirdo
mouth travels fast are you an early
os ieiunium transeat ad vos mane
adopter of the Nintendo switch or any
aut quid de Nintendo switch adopter
other product that has been a
alia uber quod fuerit
disappointment for you we'd love to hear
fallere te youd 'amo audire nos
comment below no Dennis made a good
Non est bonum comment below Dennis
point is no they're going to make you
ipsi erant 'iens ut te iam non est
buy an upgraded one right because it's
quod suus 'unus recte emere upgraded
like you see a PlayStation like for them
sicut vides in tempus est sed sapien simile eis
playstation 4 pro yeah are they going to
pro Playstation IV ad yeah sunt
have like a pro the new switch + yeah no
quasi novi habent pro switch non yeah +
dead pixels how long have your upset you
mortuus pixels turbaverunt vos habere quousque
thought you're going to get in the versa
cogitavi ut vos erant 'iens ad converso;
alright thanks for watching the category
licet ad gratiam spectant genus
5 TV news room don't forget to Like and
V locus nolite oblivisci TV News and Agnus Dei
subscribe for all your tech news with a
subscribe pro omnibus vobis cum tech nuntium
slight Linux bias and for more free
Pondus et liberius tenui Linux
content be sure to check out our website
Lorem website contentus esse
from the category 5 TV news room I'm
V cubiculum Im 'genus ab TV News
splashed are made of
factum est autem residuam fudit sunt,
[Music]
[Musica]
[Applause]
[Plausus]